啊你干嘛
我上厕所啊
你闭着眼睛上
我闭着眼睛怎么上
干嘛你就这样上
哎呦哎呀你这样我怎么上厕所
也就我接走
你看着点哎呀我知道
好了没啊
等一下磨磨唧唧
好像好了
好了你可以出去了哎呀
怎么我上厕所就得眼蒙着
你得眼睁着
你不要跟我讲话我有洁癖
哼
哼都是我爱吃的
不至于吧
你这样真是太用损我形象了
现在不是没有人吗
有人的话我会注意的
不行从现在开始
你的一言一行都要尽量学我
听到没嗯
有人来了主心想范总
楼台的车还有一个小时就到庄园了
一切已经安排好了
奶奶
什么
啊范总
我想应该是您明天订婚
所以你的奶奶想提前过来看看哦
奶奶来了
要不你先下去安排我马上过去
好的
嘿嘿嘿
Ah what are you doing
I'm going to the bathroom
You close your eyes
How can I do it with my eyes closed?
Why are you doing this?
Ouch, oops, how can I go to the toilet like this?
I'll take it.
Look at it, oops, I know
Are you ready?
Wait a minute
It seems to be fine
Ok you can go out oops
Why do I have to go to the toilet blindfolded?
You have to keep your eyes open.
Don't talk to me I'm a neat freak
Humph
Hmm, it's all my favorite food
I don't think so.
You are really destroying my image like this.
Isn't there no one now?
I'll pay attention if anyone
No. From now on
You should try to imitate me in every word and deed
Did you hear that?
Someone is here, thinking of Mr. Fan
The car on the platform will arrive at the manor in an hour
Everything has been arranged
grandma
What!
Ah Mr. Fan
I think it should be your engagement tomorrow.
So your grandma wants to come and have a look in advance.
Grandma is here
Why don't you go down and arrange it first, I'll be there right away
Okay
Hey, hey, hey.